泰
好
喀
西門町 國賓戲院 後門巷子內
泰式炸雞塊
大腸包小腸
透心涼飲品
讚
裝甲監獄火車
我們抓回逃犯了.
我們在返回監獄的途中.
鄧紮裏 監獄
Lucky ring's on.
幸運戒指戴上了.
I feel so much safer.
我感到無比安心呀
Raving! We are coming in high.
伊哈！ 我們來啦.
Hold on!
抓穩了！
Clear!
安全！
Let's go!
走吧！
What's the hold up?
摸什麼呢？
Nothing, we are on our way.
沒事，我們馬上到.
Let's go!
快啦！
Your dude's tripping.
你朋友有夠盧.
Doc!
醫生！
Forget this!   Evacuate!
別鳥他了！ 快閃！
I'm not leaving him!
我不能丟下他.
Doc!
醫生！
Bomb!
快爆啦！
浴血任務Ⅲ
Oh, you just screwed up on me, ah?
你想整死我，對吧？
After 8 damned years.
靠 八年了.
What's up with that?
搞屁呀？
You know black house prision doesn't officially exist.
你知道黑房監獄，並非官方所有.
I just got the location from a guy named "Church".
我從〝恰吉〞口中打聽到位置.
An agency spook.
一個幽靈部門.
Excuse me?
蝦咪？
The agency's official, relax!
這部門是官方的，放心！
I think you're the timebomb, man.
我覺得你是定時炸彈，兄弟.
What a wast of life.
真是浪費生命.
You made one damned mistake.
你犯了個該死的錯誤.
Was it a mistake?
那是個錯誤？
You stupid, if you've done that to me, I would chapter you into pieces.
蠢蛋，若你對我那樣，我就把你大卸八塊.
You would try!
你試試！
Hey, you wanna thank the guys?
你該感謝這些兄弟吧？
The guys?
兄弟？
Where are our guys?
我們的兄弟呢？
Pema?   Wutzby?
佩瑪？ 伍茲比？
Gone.
走了.
Dead gone?
掛了？
Yeah.
是的.
Heard you kill more people than the plague.
聽說你比瘟疫殺的人還多.
How about that?
那又怎麼樣？
Why they call you "Dr. Death"?
為什麼他們叫你〝死神醫生〞？
Used to be a medic.
曾經是一名醫生.
But that was a long time ago.
但那是很久以前的事了.
So why did you get locked away?
為何你會被鎖起來？
Tax evasion.
逃漏稅.
So you're all this left expendables?
浴血團只剩你們了？
We are it.
沒錯.
We started with 5.
浴血團草創時有5人.
Built up to 22.
最多有22人
I see Barney is still hanging the tags up there.
我看到巴尼仍將兵籍牌掛在那邊.
See that Jingling sound that tags' making?
你聽到兵籍牌發出的叮噹聲了嗎？
That's remind that our....
那是提醒我們…
brothers... are still here.
兄弟們…依舊在…
Somewhere.
某處.
Come on, wacky.
來吧，怪咖.
Give old screw your blade.
刀子借用一下.
Or she might find your tags up there.
否則你的兵籍牌也會掛在上面.
Jingling too. Jingling~
也會叮噹響. 叮叮噹～
Sharp it when you've done.
用完記得磨利.
Your friend's a little lof.
你的朋友有點瘋了.
Come on, Christmas. He's been in a hole for years.
別這樣，耶誕節  他在洞裏呆了8年.
And I guess he's so lucky?
怎麼這麼幸運？
They try to pulling off the half-assed political assassination...
他們在瑞士為了幾美元…
for a few bucks in this place called Switzerland.
想完成一個愚蠢的政治暗殺.
And they blew it!
最後搞砸了！
Self-destructive.
自我毀滅.
Yeah, someting like that.   But...
嗯，的確是. 但…
You know that he is a good medic.
他是個好醫生.
All I've done is to check up.
我就是想調查清楚.
Why are you so sarcastic?
為何你就愛譏諷人呢？
You're fake.
你個騙子.
Vague?
說的不清楚？
Secrets, idiot!
秘密，白癡！
Why do you take me off away around the planet...
為何帶我繞了大半個地球…
to save this...
去救這個…
Medic genius what you describe.
你所謂的天才醫生？
For What?
為何？
He's expendable.
他是浴血團成員.
Come on!
少來！
Is it Expendable?
這不就是浴血團精神嗎？
So he's one of the flock.
所以他是我們中的一員了？
Let me tell you something, if you are in car threat for years.
這麼說吧，若你多年來害怕坐車.
I'll come to save you.
我也會來救你的.
Thanks, hero.
感恩，英雄.
But I doubt it.
但我才不信呢.
I know you'll do the same for me.
我知道你也會救我的.
Truthfully?
真的嗎？
You let me ride?
你會讓我開嗎？
Exactly.
當然.
Hey, Doc.
嘿，醫生.
What's your name?
你叫什麼名字？
Christmas.
耶誕節.
Is that Real?
真名嗎？
Authentic.
如假包換.
Is that real too?
這紋身也是真的嗎？
Oh, no, I...
哦，不，我…
spend 3 hours every morning...
每天早上花3小時…
put this on a black biro.
把手放在黑色圓珠筆上弄的.
This is real.
這是真的.
Authentic.
貨真價實.
Riginal, look at that.
原創的，瞧瞧
Oh, balence's a little off.
噢，平衡感退步了.
You are a knife man?
你是刀手嗎？
Best.
頂尖.
Ever.
絕無僅有.
I'm the knife man before christmas.
我在有耶誕節日之前就用刀了.
Is that right, Barney?
是不是，巴尼？
If you say so.
你說了就算.
Probably fish out and when the blade while use to suck on your dady's teats,
可能我掏出刀，刀子已經在舔你父親的乳頭.
you're trying to learn how to eat with the scoop
而你還在學如何用勺子吃東西.
Yeah...
是哦…
A lot of secrets you're still keeping on, Mr. my lord?
你的秘密挺多的啊，老大先生？
Just stay on my brains.
留在我腦子裏了.
Tell you, I can't wait to get home.
真的，我等不及要返家了.
Eats good food.
吃大餐.
put on some fun dress.
穿酷酷的衣服.
break up my 49 Pontiac
拆開我的皮蒂亞克49
keep that baby till that engine blows up.
開著它直到引擎操爆錶.
You didn't tell him, did you?
你還沒告訴他，對嗎？
Tell me what?
告訴我什麼？
We are not going home.
我們不回家.
We'll stop a dude named Victor Mins'...
我們要阻止這名維克多•銘斯…
delivering a ship of thermobaric bombs.
走私整船熱壓炸彈.
Oh, come on, man.
哦，哇嘞，兄弟.
That shit is hell fire.
這是燙手山芋.
Hey, routine stuff.
只是例行公事.
Why do you just pick me up on you way back?
你們為何不先辦完之後再接我？
We are man short.
我們人手不足.
Well, you know, I love the party with you boys.
我很喜歡跟兄弟們一起幹.
But...
但是…
I don't have much shit.
我沒有裝備啊.
Oh.
哦.
That's my shit!
這是我的裝備！
It is your shit.
是你的裝備.
Doc.
醫生
Will You thank the guys... that helping you up？
你得感謝一下那些…幫你的兄弟吧？
Say something.
誠心點.
Listen up.
各位.
It's been a long time since I have the reason to say..
長久以來，我想跟大家說…
Thank you.
感謝！
So I just wanna...
所以我只是想…
You know, I...
你們懂的，我…
The kid's resumed.
這傢伙恢復了.
Thank you.
謝謝你們！
sincerely over warming.
超感動的…
I think I'm gonna weep.
我都快哭了.
You know what?   Enough.
夠了，就此打住.
Don't be so sarcastic. Yeah, that was great.
別挖苦了，他說的很棒.
Doc, it's realy good.
醫生，說的很好.
You gotta talked for a long time.
你說了長篇大論.
You got the gift.
有演講天賦.
So you heard?
你聽見了？
It's like riding a bike.
像騎車般流暢.
To me it's like judging the best moment.
對我來說真動人.
Very aggressive.
很震撼.
I've made my point.
我說到重點了.
That move me, I'm moved.
我感動了.
I moved you too?
你也感動你嗎？
Stunning delivering.
很好的表達.
Stunning.
非常棒.
Doc!
醫生！
Yeah!
是！
Great to have you back.
真高興你回來了.
No better place to be, yeah!
沒有比這更好的地方了…
摩加迪沙，索馬里
I told you boys to slow up.
我叫你們別太張揚.
Nice boat.
船很小巧.
Thanks ladys, I stoled it myself.
謝謝誇獎，我偷的.
We got 3 more like this patrolling the harbor.
還有三個像這樣的巡守碼頭
2 man ground team every 400 meters.
每四百公尺有二名衛兵.
Good work.
幹的好.
Just because you can flying a plane don't make you smarter than me.
別以為你會開飛機就比我聰明.
Sure, it does.
當然，你最棒.
So you're the reason I've been stuck in the hand of this shit hole.
原來就是你小子，害我在這鬼地方等這麼久。
Shit hole?
鬼地方？
Brother, you have no idea.
大哥，你才不暸何謂鬼地方.
Oh, yeah.
哦，真屌.
What the hell is that?
那是什麼鬼？
This bitch solves all your problems.
這玩意能解決你所有難題.
Yeah, maybe for 10 seconds.
呿，最多撐十秒.
We'll blow it, let's watch.
我們等著看他出糗.
Now, you got that problem too?
你現在也想吐槽我嗎？
You work out that one.
你宰了那小子吧.
Make it out...
出發吧…
Good luck.
祝你好運.
It's all under control.
一切在掌控之中.
Yeah, that's what it looks like.
嗯，看起來是的.
Where'd you've been?
你去哪了？
I had an doctor appointment.
我跟醫生去約會.
This is what you boys need.
你們需要開路先鋒
Where's he going?
他去哪？
Watch over head.
注意上方.
Doc, go!
醫生，去吧！
Oh, silly, the man attacked me with a knife.
哦，靠北，這傢伙竟只用刀宰了我！
Damn, he's good.
靠，真屌.
Yeah, better than you.
嗯，比你牛.
You gotta want to see this.
你得來瞧瞧.
See what?
看三小？
I'll show you.
秀給你看.
Damn, he's realy good.
靠，超級屌.
Say that again, I'll shoot you.
再說，我就扁你.
Show?
秀啥？
Get in.
進來.
Where's the bomb?
炸彈在哪？
They'll be there.
可能在那邊.
Barney, looks like our target has finally come.
巴尼，看來我們的目標終於到了.
Guys, men, let's take him fast.
兄弟們，先發制人.
Barney, gotta put you down.
巴尼，要放下你們了.
It can't be.
不會吧.
What can't be?
怎麼了？
Will you shoot this guy or not?
你到底要不要斃了它？
What's the hold up?
拖什麼呢？
He's dead.
他早就死了.
Who's dead?
誰死了？
Stonebanks.
史通班克斯
Stonebanks!
史通班克斯！
- Come on, get in, get in....     - Come on, let's move.
-快點，進來，進來.  -快點，我們走.
Go, go, go
走～
Come on!
快呀！
Time to blow them all!
該把他們都轟了！
Told you. 10 seconds.
看吧，就十秒.
Hang on, I'll give you a ride.
抓緊，我給你搞一輛車.
Time to go.
該閃了.
Come on!
快點！
Go, go, go.
走～
How much do we get payed for this?
我們這一票能撈多少？
Not enough.
沒幾兩.
Go right.
右轉.
You're not gonna hit.
你衝不過去的
Always negative.
沒有不可能.
I'll get car sick.
我要暈車了.
Hang on, doc. on your side.
撐住，醫生. 有敵人.
Medic!
醫生！
Get out!
出來吧
Come on.
走吧.
Caesar, we're coming to your way.
凱撒，我們往你那邊去了.
Where are you?
你在哪？
The dirty river behind you.
你背後的臭水溝.
Try to stay as closer as you can.
儘量靠近一點.
Make a room for Caesar.
留個位子給我.
Move your asses.
快閃哪.
Bullshit!   What's that?
哇嘞！ 銃三小？
A huge pal carry out a boat.
我們大卡車飛來橫船.
Hold it, hold it, you're gotta going.
控制方向，繼續前進.
You're alright?
你還好嗎？
Yeah
很好.
Pull over.
停車.
Incoming!
完彈了！
Move, move!
快跑.
Hang on, come on!
撐住，加油！
Barney!
巴尼～
Maybe this will bring you luck.
或許戒指能帶給你好運.
Is he gonna make it?
他能撐得過嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道.
Who did this?
這是誰幹的？
Stonebanks.
史通班克斯.
I thought you've killed him.
我記得你早就殺了他.
So did I.
我也以為.
He shot Caesar, he'll get back in me.
他射殺凱撒，他將會找我報仇.
You know, I'm getting out of this business.
你知道，我早已金盆洗手.
And so should you.
你也該退了.
Not yet.
時候未到.
Hey.
嘿…
If you need some help...   It's Stonebanks!
若需幫忙…  對手是史通班克斯！
I'm supposed to meet a guy named "Church".
我該見的是位叫〝恰吉〞的人.
I know who you are.
我知道你是誰.
So who are you?
那你又是誰？
Operational officer "Drummer".
作戰官〝莊墨〞.
You don't have to worry about Church any more.
你無須再擔心恰吉了
He is....
他已…
out of the picture.
不幹了.
Jesus Ross!
天哪，羅斯！
What a mess.
天翻地覆.
We gave you everything.
我們給了你一切.
Target, opportunity.
目標、時機.
All the intelligence you could ask for it.
你需要的所有情報.
and you got...
而你卻…
decimated.
大開殺戒.
And my target walked away.
然後我的目標跑了.
Am I wrong?   Am I missing something?
我有說錯嗎？ 還是漏了什麼？
Yeah.
是的.
Church said the target's name was "Victor Mins".
恰吉說：目標名叫〝維克多•銘斯〞.
And?
然後呢？
He was wrong.
他搞錯了.
His real name is "Conrad Stonebanks".
他的真名是〝康拉德•史通班克斯〞.
We know him only as "Victor Mins".
我們只知他叫〝維克多•銘斯〞.
Arms dealer, made billions, selling to every cycle overlord in Africa and the Middle East.
軍火商，賺取數十億美元，把武器賣給非洲和中東地區的土匪頭子
His own mercenaries of army's personally responsible..
他親點的雇傭兵團…
For torturing and killing.
拷打與虐殺了…
two of the best men I've ever knew, friends.
我認識的兩位元最好部屬、摯友.
I don't give a shit what his name is.
我才不管他叫什麼鬼.
I don't like him.
我不喜歡他.
I want him as bad as you do.
我跟你一樣恨之入骨.
This happened on my watch.
一切都在我監控之下
You fucked up.
你卻搞砸了.
And I'm wearying it.
我無語問天.
I'll find him...again!
我會再找到他！
You have one more shot.
你還有一次機會.
Nice to find that major work.
很高興我們能合作.
Your men are shot to shit.
你兄弟都潰不成軍.
What do you gonna do for a team?
你打算怎麼再組隊？
Don't worry about it, I'll handle it.
別擔心，我會搞定的.
Relax.
放輕鬆.
You would give yourself a stroke.
否則會把自己搞中風的.
What's with these guys?
這些傢伙怎麼了？
Would you mind?
借過好嗎？
莫斯科，俄羅斯
Do you think when the artist painted this, he ever though of goals such ridiculous price?
你認為當藝術家畫這幅畫時，有想過價格會如此荒謬嗎？
I mean what is it?   Just some paint, brushes, some cheap canvas.
我是說，它是什麼？ 就只是顏料、畫筆，和便宜的畫布.
What's the big deal?
有啥了不起？
It's shit. What do you want for it?
這幅鳥畫. 你開價多少錢？
3 million.
300萬.
Done.
成交.
You know, it's very hard for me to say this, but
有些話我很難說出口，但…
at one time,
曾經
You guys were the best.
你們是最頂尖的.
Maybe still are.
也許身手依舊.
But nothing lasts forever.
但曲終人亦散.
Hard as it is to hear.
這話雖很難聽.
We're not to future anymore.
我們無法再同甘共苦了.
Unfortunate for us.
衰運連連.
We're part of the past
我們是老古董了.
You are... you're not solving with us?
你…你不跟我們一起解決此事？
As I say it.
如我所說.
If we keep this life up,
若我們要繼續生活…
the only way this thing ends.
此事到此結束
For all of us.
為全體都好
It is a hole in the ground, and no one gives a shit.
眼不見為淨，才是上上策.
Now, if that's the way I supposed to go up, I can live with that.
現在，若這是我該繼續走的路，我絕不逃避.
For me.
就我而言.
But what I can't live with
但我無法忍受
you won't live with.
你們亦不想接受
is taking you with me.
就是帶著你們一起幹.
What are you saying?   It's our call.
你說蝦咪？ 決定權在我們吧.
I'm changing things now.
我改變心意了.
You.
你.
Me
我.
All of us.
所有人.
It's over.
結束了.
We've done.
我們玩完了.
Done?
玩完了？
You break me out?   Cut me loose?
你幫我越獄？ 放我出來？
You'll survive.
你會活下去.
You all will.
你們都會活下去.
Live your life all you can.
去過你們想要的生活吧.
Where're you going, Barney?
你要去哪，巴尼？
Are you saying you just put a plug in that, that's it?
你剛剛說你只是把洞堵住，就這樣？
Just did.
就是.
Yeah?
是嗎？
But it doesn't what I want.
但這非我所願.
What?
怎樣？
We've been through the mud.
我們走過泥地.
The shit! The blood!  I've saved your ass more times than I count.
血都白流了嗎？ 我救你太多次，都數不清了.
You owe me a shot to the son of bitch's tooking Caesar down.
你得為凱撒中槍報仇.
We are not doing that.
我們不報仇了.
I'm enjoying it.
我很喜歡浴血團.
Enjoying for the whole ride.
享受整個旅程.
I know you did.
我知道你很喜歡.
But it's over.
但浴血團解散了.
拉斯維加斯，內華達州
Bonaparte.
波拿巴.
Sorry to hear about "Caesar".
聽到〝凱撒〞出事，我很難過.
I hope he's supposed to be the good one, and the good ones are rare.
希望他證明了自己很強，而且是強中之王.
Yeah.
是的.
Well, here we are again. What do you need?
你又來找我. 有何貴幹？
A new team.
新的團隊.
I'm tired of the old ones.
我厭倦了舊的團隊.
Welcome to the 21st century.
歡迎來到21世紀.
What guys are you looking for?
想找哪種傢夥？
Young, Hungry.
年輕、饑渴.
Willing to take a bullet.
願意擋子彈.
We're going up for Stonebanks.
我們要去追捕〝史通班克斯〞.
Stonebanks?
史通班克斯？
Let's see I'm not the only one sleeping that much.
還好我不是唯一宿醉未醒之人
Stonebanks dead, my friend, mortals did.
〝史通班克斯〞死了，老友. 是人都會死.
No, he is not.
不，他沒死.
That's not good.
代誌不妙.
It's a half used to be 4 or 5 men and you got a cut.
以前4、5個人選，你都砍一半.
You gonna need 50.
這次你得需要50個人選.
You gotta move fast, no time.
動作快，沒時間了.
If I gotta do it fast, I can't guarantee the best.
若我隨便挑，就沒品質保證.
Just give me some that don't give it to him.
只需要給我一些他沒有的.
Well, it's a one way ticket.
好吧，只好這樣了.
Could be.
是的.
Fine.
好吧.
I got in line of a few head cases.
我手邊有些頭號人選.
Probably these guys are prying of shooting themselves.
可能這些傢伙是自己花錢找死.
Wait.
等待.
What about these guys?   They are anything?
這些傢伙如何？ 矯健嗎？
These guys are pussy.
這些傢伙都是娘們.
大提頓山，懷俄明州
He calls by "Thorn",
他叫〝索恩〞.
expert hacker, pro pilot.
駭客，專業飛行員.
Their team must be hacking in the Seattle operating system.
他們團隊駭進了西雅圖的作業系統.
trapped down the whole city for 3 days.
癱瘓了全市整整3天.
Why the hell would he do that?
他幹嘛這樣搞？
As he can.
臭屁啊.
What?
怎樣？
I'm not looking for an office worker.
我不是來找上班族的.
That's not him.
不是他.
That's him.
在上面.
Another one with a death wish.
另一個找死的傢伙.
You two got a lot in common.
你們倆有很多共同之處.
I could do that.
我也能爬的.
You know what, I'll come right on saying...
知道嗎，我想說的是…
I belong on you.
我是你的.
Come on.
來吧.
You can't do that.
你辦不到.
No.
沒錯.
We'll specially read on that one.
特別留意一下這傢伙.
Yeah, yeah, as it payed.
嗯，是，我會的.
Always on the damn road going some places you don't wanna give a damn about.
總是在前往根本不在乎的某處途中.
Be standstill.
淡定.
Yeah, I got 2 exwives and 3 kids are lost my number will disagree.
是的，我有意見相左且不聯絡的2個前妻3個小孩
Hey, did you turn off the auto pilot.
嘿，你是不是關掉自動駕駛了？
I don't touch the auto pilot.
我根本沒碰它.
Maybe it's loose.
也許是按鈕鬆了.
Are we of course?
我說對了？
Where the hell are we?
我們到底在哪？
Hang on a second.
等等.
Is that... Is that the big dipper?
那…是北斗星嗎？
Yeah, We gotta turn around.
是的，我們必須掉頭.
Woah.
喔～
紐約市
Next candidate is an expert in field crafting and close quarters combat.
下個候選人是偽裝及近身搏擊的高手.
- Luna.     - Hi.
-露娜.  -你好.
I miss you, young lady, meet a friend of mine: Barney Ross.
美女，好久不見，見見我朋友：巴尼•羅斯
Barney Ross, Luna; Luna, Barney Ross.
巴尼，這是露娜；露娜，這是巴尼.
Nice to meet you, Mr Ross.
羅斯先生，很高興認識你.
Gentlemen, follow me.   I'll be take a waiting.
先生們，跟我來. 正等你們呢.
Come on, a little loud.
來吧，有點吵.
So, Luna, how is it these days?
露娜，別來無恙？
You know, gets old.
變老了.
Forget there. Excuse me.
不好意思，失陪一下.
All right, so what do we do here?
好吧，我們在這幹嘛？
Have a drink.
喝一杯.
Where's the candidate?
候選人嘞？
Right there, with red dress and about to chop those guys now.
在那，穿紅衣服的，正要去扁那幫傢伙.
Hostess?
女老闆？
Not the hostess.
非一般女老闆
She is a bouncer.
她是進擊的巨人.
I can do that.
我也行的.
You wanna slip on her dress and give a shot?
你敢穿她的裙裝打打看嗎？
Man!
沒擋頭！
She's good.
她很棒.
You ought see her without heels.
她不穿高跟鞋更猛.
阿帕奇 江喀申，亞利桑那州
When's your last checkup?
你上次體檢是何時？
I don't know, a while back.
不知道，有段時間了.
High cholesterol, plaque, all that stuff?
高膽固醇、血糖之類的嗎？
Yeah, pretty much.
是的，差不多.
Yeah.
是的.
Except with me.
我也是…
I found a lump in my lung.
我發現肺有腫塊.
Very darkness sad.
位置很隱蔽.
Why shouldn't I see that coming?
為何我沒及早發現呢？
Well, What will you do?
嗯，你有何打算？
I tryed to make much more money as I can.
我設法盡力賺更多錢.
as fast as I can.
加快速度.
Yeah.
是的.
But those kids, you know, the ones, don't talk to them.
但是那幫小弟，一個也別告訴他們.
Make some kind of good impression on it...when I'm gone.
在我死前，留個好印象給他們.
Sad enough?
難過嗎？
Yeah, It is sad.
是的，很難過.
Sorry.
抱歉.
Asshole, Bullshit, I'm fine.
混蛋，誆你的，我好的很.
What?
什麼？
Just check you're still human.
只是看你還有沒有人性.
How did you gonna believe? Didn't that?
你還真相信了嗎？
Yeah, you did. God damned.
是，你贏了  該死的.
- That can never happen again, I'll never trust you again.     - All right.
-別再想騙我，我永遠不再信你了.  -好啦.
Next kid's a bed of dark horse.
下個傢伙是匹黑馬.
Just came cross my desk, I like throwing in a wildcard.
驚鴻一瞥的王牌，要好好珍藏.
But this guy's creds are too bad to pass up.
但這傢伙的事跡倒是不容錯過.
Anybody seen Felipe?
有人看到菲力浦嗎？
Yo, Felipe!
嘿，菲力浦！
Those are good, Bonaparte.
身手靈活，波拿巴.
Yeah, not bad.
是，不錯
Yeah, you find the guy right.
嗯，你找對人了.
Damn.
屌.
Felipe Silva.
費利佩•席爾瓦.
Meet Barney Ross.
這是巴尼•羅斯.
Galgo?
嘎戈？
You sent me another fake resume?
你又寄假履歷給我？
Mr. Ross.
羅斯先生.
I can do what you need, whatever you need.
我能做您要求的任何事.
I am healthy than I look.
我比外貌更健康.
Stronger than I look.
比外表更強壯.
Faster than I look.
比外型更快.
Shit, You were born in 1984?
鬼扯，你三十歲嗎？
Of course not.
當然不是.
But I feel like I was born in 1984.
但我自認三十歲.
Do not waste your time. Barney, we'll leave.
別費神了. 巴尼，我們走吧.
Mr Ross, Mr Ross, Mr Ross, please!
羅斯先生～ 拜託啦！
It's like... It's like to have discovered the founding of youth.
這有如…發現了〝回春泉〞.
I mean not the... "Founding Of Youth".
我不是指那…〝長生不老泉〞.
Ponce De Leon discovered that one.
那個泉是龐塞•德利昂發現的.
By the way.
順帶一提.
Another great spanish like myself.
我亦是超優的西班牙人.
But as you know.
但如您所知.
Mr. Ross.
羅斯先生.
Age... is just a state of mind.
年齡…只是一種心態.
Only you're old when you surrender, when you give up.
唯有您內心投降或放棄了，才算變老.
And I haven't, not yet.
而我沒有，尚未.
- Galgo, the shit has got to be stopped.     - I gotta go
-嘎戈，掰夠了，該停了.  -我走了
This is the third time this month.
這是本月第三次了.
Seriously, move on.
說真的，閃遠點.
This guy has a story.
這傢伙有故事啊.
Actually I feel a little sorry for him.
事實上，我對他有點抱歉.
His Last team dropped him.
上個團隊拋棄了他.
Back in day, you couldn't catch him.
在過去，你根本抓不住他.
Very fast, maybe faster than you.
非常快，或許快過你.
No way.
屁咧.
Oh, maybe.
哦，真的.
But what I'm gonna say...
但我仍得說…
It's a young man's game.
這是年輕人的工作.
I need a job.
我需要工作.
All I know what to do is killing people.
我唯一會做的就是殺人.
And I do not fail one.
而我從未失手.
God damn it!
ㄊㄇㄉ！
愛德華茲空軍基地，加利福尼亞
So what's story on this guy?
這個傢伙又是什麼來歷？
I found him at DARPA.
我在〝高防局〞找到他的.
DARPA?
〝高防局〞？
Sounds like a town in North Africa.
聽起來像北非的小鎮.
"Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency."
〝美國國防部高級研究專案局〞.
They send the brightest military minds to develop next-generation weapons.
他們把最聰明的軍事專員，送去研發新一代武器.
Google it.
上網查.
I'm not looking for a weapon's nerd.
我不是要找紙上談兵仔.
Ah, Then you come to the right place.
啊，那你來對地方了.
Yo, Marito.
喲，馬里多.
Mars, I'm gonna like you to meet Barney Ross.
馬斯，來見見巴尼•羅斯.
And shooters have got all Mars' gift as they get.
槍手具備的天賦，馬斯與生俱來.
Whatever you say.
過獎了.
What do you say?
你的說法呢？
What I got here is an excellent 25mm assault rifle.
我有一挺頂級25mm突擊步槍
laser range, 25mm high explosive variable traps.
雷射瞄準，攜帶25mm高爆變量彈.
It can be programs to detonate over and behind the target.
它可同時引爆目標物上方與後方之物件.
He'll do.
簽下他.
華瑞茲，墨西哥
Final candidate, John Smilee.
最終候選人，約翰•斯麥利.
The guy's got most team the end of the street.
這傢伙是街上有最多團隊的人.
A lot of skills, Marines, specially operator
多項戰技，海軍陸戰隊員，很特別的行家
But, there is an issue.
但是，有個小怪癖…
What issue?
什麼問題？
Yeah, classic, a authority problem but..
哦，典型的，權威主義問題，但…
There's a cup of more sweeping around you're about to.
對你來說小事一樁.
Sorry, Barney, I'm wasting your time. And this is not the guy I though with.
抱歉，巴尼. 耽誤你時間了，這傢伙跟我想的不一樣.
No.
不.
I wanna meet him.
我想見他.
John.
約翰.
Meet Barney Ross.
這是巴尼•羅斯.
You didn't do much to impress up today, did you?
你今天表現不太正常，對吧？
You called me, I didn't call you.
你聯絡我的，我又沒聯絡你.
Think you'd die for the money?
你想為錢而死嗎？
Maybe you would like it when you asked from the strangers.
或許陌生人的錢你更想賺.
What do you guys want for me?
你們要我幹什麼？
You're running for something?
你在逃避什麼？
I don't know you.
我不認識你.
But I know you.
但我認識你.
Oh, Yeah?
噢，是嗎？
How's that?
那又如何？
Maybe you think you got more potential, but we're short on time.
或許你自認潛力無限，但我們沒啥時間.
Is that about it, right?
是這樣，對吧？
Yeah, That's about it.
嗯，沒錯.
You know, That's your problem.
嘿拎刀ㄟ代誌.
And your problem is you're going around the dirt for chump change.
你的問題是在泥中翻滾只為蠅頭小利.
I heard you lost a few friends in the desert.
我聽說你在沙漠失去了一些朋友.
They aboard it.
杳無音信.
You didn't, you were the guilt.
你生還，卻深感愧疚.
I've been there.
我經歷過.
He's been there.
他也經歷過.
We've all lived it.
我們都是過來人.
Well, You don't know me.
嗯，你根本不瞭解我.
I know the type.
我懂你格性.
Bonaparte, you are right.
波拿巴，你對了.
You did wast my time.
真的浪費功夫.
Hey.
嘿…
You didn't wast your time.
你們沒有白忙.
If you're going after Stonebanks, we might wanna talk about the financials now.
若你要追捕史通班克斯，那我們就該先談酬勞了.
Normally just 10%, but..
一般只收10%頭款，但…
I figure if Stonebanks is in the equation,
我認為既然是史通班克斯，相對的…
I might wanna get all my fees.
我覺得把費用全歸我吧.
Possiblly now.
最好現在就給.
All right.
好吧.
I mean not you the good for it.
我不是觸你黴頭.
Just, if you don't mind.
只是，若你不介意的話.
I don't mind.
我不介意.
Sounds like you don't have too much faith in me.
似乎你對我沒啥信心啊.
I don't.
沒錯.
How was your vacation?
假期過的如何？
Ready to go to work?
準備上工了嗎？
Did you find him yet?
人找到了嗎？
He's in Bucharest putting together a deal with someone Albanian mobster.
他在布加勒斯特，跟某位元阿爾巴尼亞匪徒一起談交易.
You got 36 hours, that's your window.
你有36小時的空檔.
After that, he's back off the grid.
錯過，他從此消失.
Satellite map, coordinates for where he'll be.
衛星地圖，他所在的座標.
Interesting guy.
有趣的傢伙.
Your friend Stonebanks.
你的好友 史通班克斯.
You're not gonna like this but...
你可能不喜歡這樣，但…
They want him alive.
他們想抓活的.
Are you kidding me?
你在耍我吧？
They want to try him at The Hague.
他們想把他送到海牙國際法庭.
中央情報局
機密檔案
For war crimes.
以戰犯審判.
You let me give this guy a chance to court?
你要我給這傢夥機會上法庭嗎？
It's not my decision.
這不是我的決定.
No... it never is.
對…皆非你願.
- That's a way it's got to be.     - Right.
-這是指令，必須完成  -好吧.
Agency's got a local safe house.
情報局有個當地的避難所.
You gonna need it.
你需要的.
Don't trash the place.
別摧毀了.
Heard you got a job.
聽說你有任務了.
That's right.
是的.
Who the hell are they?
他們是誰？
They'll do with me.
他們和我一起幹.
And we are not?
我們不一起幹？
You're right. Told you everything I did tell you back in the bar.
是的，在酒吧我就已經說的很清楚了.
Stop drinking so much.
別喝這麼多酒.
You wanna get yourself killed.
你自尋死路.
With those youngsters.
還拖群小鬼.
Do us all a favor, get the hell out of here.
幫幫忙，快離開這吧.
We'll start up in 10:00.
我們十點出發.
Come on.
來吧.
You guys want to fight.
你的兄弟們想出征.
Why didn't they just get married?
為何他們不去結婚呢？
You're seriously smoking, that's the aviation fuel.
你真敢抽煙，這些是航空燃油.
Amateur.
業餘的.
Amateur assholes.
業餘的混蛋們.
Who'd you call asshole, grandpa?
你叫誰混蛋呢，爺爺？
Grandpa's about to crash your windpipe.
爺爺要捏斷你的氣管.
What's this?
這是什麼？
Is it your toy?
你的玩具嗎？
Boy.
小弟弟.
You wanna dance, big guy?
你想跳舞嗎，大老粗？
Hey!
嘿！
It's just a job.
只是一份工作.
Come on, Let's go.
好啦，我們走吧.
Bunch of has been's still trying to be hard.
一群老鬼，來點真功夫吧.
Yeah, you're young and you're dumb.
是的，你們少不更事.
Jingling!
響叮噹！
Keep it.
留著吧.
You gonna need it.
你會需要的.
Never thought you would call in that favor.
真沒想到你會找我幫忙.
I'm so happy about it.
我也很高興你能來.
Got a minute?
有空嗎？
What do you need?
有何貴幹？
Tell me more about this guy we're going after.
說說我們要追捕的這個傢伙的來歷.
It doesn't matter, you're hired to do a job.
無關緊要，你只是拿錢消災的.
How about answering why we're doing this job?
不然說說我們為何要淌這渾水？
I owe you a salary that's it.
我欠你薪資，如此而已.
Why are we going after Stonebanks?
我們為何要追捕史通班克斯？
You have a hard time taking orders, don't you?
你很難聽從指揮，是嗎？
If I don't know what they are yet.
若我不知原因，恕難從命.
I know you don't give a damn about us.
我知道你不在乎我們幾個.
I get that.
我懂的.
But just tell me why you wanna take out this guy so bad?
但是請告訴我，為何你急於抓這傢伙？
♫ Aloe Blacc 《 Ticking Bomb 》
♪ The Whole world sitting on a ticking bomb. ♪
♪ So keep your calm, carry on. ♪
♪ Sun may never rise again. ♪
♪ The question ain't if but when. ♪
♪ Sea will mourn and the sky will fall. ♪
♪ The sun may never rise again. ♪
♪ The silent war has begun. ♪
♪ The staring down loaded gun. ♪
♪ No refuge found no solid ground. ♪
♪ Assuming race can't be one. ♪
♪ Don't wait to say goobye, you're running out of time. ♪
♪ Whatever you believe it's easy to see. ♪
♪ The Whole world sitting on a ticking bomb. ♪
♪ And it's about to explode. Oh~ ♪
30 seconds to drop.
30秒後跳傘.
Copy that.
收到.
Let's go.
出發.
I take care of myself.
我會照顧自己.
20 seconds to drop.
20秒後跳傘.
10 seconds.
10秒後跳傘.
布加勒斯特，羅馬尼亞.
Run.
行動.
This guy's got more muscles than Celtic Kings.
這傢伙肌肉比猿人還發達.
Maybe he's compensating for something.
也許他嗑了什麼補品.
What do you drink down there, Barney?   Is that like a vanilla latte or something?
巴尼，你喝什麼？ 看似香草味的拿鐵咖啡還是其他的？
Fresh of.
現磨的.
Luna, Move.
露娜，行動.
Move the car.
汽車上場.
Who's drunk?.
醉了嗎？
Nice driver, Mars.
車技一流，馬斯.
Good performance.
完美演出.
Yeah, we good.
嗯，合作無間.
Any closer, I'll beat his ass.
再近點，我就海扁他.
I believe her.
我相信.
We got him.
搞定了.
Man, This guy's protected better than the pressident.
靠，這傢伙被保護的比總統還嚴.
Yeah, and his crib's like a 5 stars fortress.
嗯，這旅館就像五星級城堡.
So we'are not taking him there.
所以我們不在那裡下手.
I bet the hotel is full of guests.
旅館裡門庭若市.
So what will we do then?
那我們要幹嘛？
At the meet.
等他們會面.
We hit from all 4 sides.
我們從四方攻擊.
hit him hard.
殺個片甲不留.
OK.
好吧.
So, our plan is to...
所以，我們的計畫是…
What, kick down the door and start spraying bullets?
踹開門，並瘋狂掃射嗎？
It's a great plan.
真是絕妙好計.
It's 1985.
這是老派作風.
What's that supposed to mean?
什麼意思？
You heard me.
明知故問.
You got a better plan.
你有妙招.
Much better.
棒多了.
Let's hear it.
洗耳恭聽.
Thorn, you're up.
索恩，你來說.
OK. I'm the plan.
好吧，我來說明
It's gotta be good.
最好行得通.
First, I hack into the security main server, bomb.
首先，我入侵安管伺服器…解除！
Bypass the motional detective lasers and biometric sensors, pow.
繞過雷射動態探測儀和生物感應器.
Overwrite the surveillance video in CCTV systems.
置換閉路電視裏的監控影像.
Ba-bam it. We are in.
輕鬆，混進去了.
It's John's play.
這就是〝約翰計畫〞.
Just like that?
如此而已？
Just like that.
簡單明瞭.
輕而易舉.
Exactly like that.
正是如此.
You'll better be right.
你最好是對的.
Ba-bam.
輕鬆.
Let's go.
走吧.
So why'd you let your team go?
你為何讓你的團隊離開？
For you still ground long enough you gonna buy, it was time.
來龍去脈妳不暸，別費神了.
They didn't seem too happy about it.
他們似乎很不爽.
If you're looking to go to a family room.
若妳將來指望走入家庭.
This's a wrong job for you.
妳選錯行業了.
There are different kinds of family.
有很多不同類型的家庭.
And when my life is on the line.
當我生命有危險時
That's my family fighting with me.
家人會和我並肩作戰.
You know what I mean.
你懂我的意思.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
嗯，我明白.
Right on time.
時間到了.
Lady first.
女士優先.
Go ahead then Thorn
哦，去吧，索恩.
Will you shut up and get in the sewer.
少囉唆，快進下水道.
And ladies and gentlemen, we officially have eyes in the sky.
麗妹帥哥，高空電子眼已就位.
Copy that.
瞭解.
Let's do this.
開幹了.
Thought you'd never ask.
還怕你不敢呢.
Good to go.
可通行.
Good luck, boys.
祝好運，哥們.
Oh, Shit!
噢，糟了！
What's the problem?
有何問題？
The buyer is early.
買家提早到了.
Threat just doubled.
威脅倍增了.
You're early.
你來早了.
What do you think?
認為如何？
It's oK.
很好.
When Cain slew his brother.
當該隱殺了他的兄弟.
God banished him from civilization.
上帝把他趕出文明社會.
But before that he placed a mark on him.
但是先給他做個標記.
That was a felonry brand, but...
那是個重罪犯的烙印，但…
it protected him from roving hunters.
它能保護他免受浪人所傷.
Customs is not X-ray artwork.
海關不會用X光照藝術品.
Ruin the oils.
會破壞顏料.
Very good.
有概念.
Then you have it.
這是你的了.
Pleasure.
交易愉快.
As always.
銀貨兩訖.
Can you access...
你能搞到…
nuclear weapons?
核武嗎？
I might.
有可能.
But generally I find people are a little too emotional for ownership.
但通常，我發現人們對所有權太情緒化.
And I hate you killing all my other customers.
我不願你宰了我其他客戶.
By accident.
無心的.
Or on purpose.
或蓄意的.
In position.
就定位.
Set.
就緒.
I'll pay you what you want.
我會如您所願.
Let me think about it.
讓我想一下.
變更同意
手動關閉程式
Run.
行動.
Stonebanks is moving.  Watch it!
史通班克斯逃了.  盯住他！
I like little mice.
我喜歡小老鼠.
Try again.
再試一次.
Open Sesame.
芝麻開門.
Go, go, go.
快走.
Move.
走.
Luna, go!
露娜，上場！
Barney Ross's well.
巴尼，搞定了.
Nice job.
幹的好.
Trench, do you copy?
陳菊，聽到了嗎？
I'm waiting.
我等著呢.
I got your security.
準備接應.
And hurry up.
快點.
It's boring.
無聊透了.
Why don't you just put a bullet in his head beyond there?
你為何不直接一槍斃了他？
Hey~ You said we are taking him alive.
嘿～ 你說我們要逮活的.
Good morning.
早安.
Are these your students?
是你的學生嗎？
Hey, kids, what'd you learned tonight, huh?
嘿，小鬼，今晚學到什麼了？
Hey, what happend to the old crew?
嘿，你的老人團怎麼了？
Oh, that's right.
哦，對了.
They stuck their noses in other peopole's worlds and got fatally injured.
他們被人牽著鼻子走，卻身負重傷.
Now they're deliverables.
現在他們被捨棄啦.
Hey.
嘿～
You hear that, kids?   Take note.
聽到了嗎，小鬼？ 噯注意哦.
Cause that's what you're doing right now.
因為你們正重蹈覆轍.
Let me shut his mouth.
讓我封了他的嘴.
You talked pretty tough to a guy who's incapacitated, which is good for you.
你跟個南冠楚囚大小聲，鳥不起.
Does it?
是嗎？
Why'd you cut me loose and I'll open your meat shirt and show your own heart?
何不放開我，我會把你開膛剖肚，讓你瞧瞧自己的心臟？
Hey, partner.
嘿，鬥陣的.
Why don't the two of us just end this?
我倆何不在此一了百了？
What do you say?
意下如何？
Makes a set up, easier, you slap mine slap and I slap yours.
來點簡單的，你呼我巴掌，我揌你耳光.
You know, make a slapping.
你懂的，呼必裂.
He thinks I'm joke, I'm not joking.
他以為我開玩笑，我不搞笑的.
You should see me when I'm angry.
你該見識我的狠樣.
It'll be very impressed.
絕對瞠目結舌.
And very dead.
死不瞑目.
So come on, pal.
來吧，老友.
Anything you wanna get off your chest?
有什麼想申冤吐氣的嗎？
Come on, lay it out.
快，說出來.
I'm a good listener.
我是個好聽眾.
You're gonna take me back to the has been crew.
你要把我帶回你夥伴那裏.
Carve me up around a fire.
大卸八塊用火烤
Very tribal.
真落後.
When we stop,
我們下機後.
I will break every bone in your body
我會讓你骨肉分離
and drop with the left at the Hague.
並送到海牙國際法庭.
The Hague?
國際法庭？
Fuck me at the big time.
天大的笑話.
I'm a war criminal.
我是戰爭罪犯.
Keep laughing.
繼續笑吧.
Do you think...
你以為…
that you can just deliver me...
可以像包裹般…
like a package?
把我送走？
We were close once.
我們曾經很嘛嘰.
See we start this holy "Expendables" thing together.
我們一起草創了〝浴血團〞.
See, I got the markers.
看，我有圖騰.
That's been faded. But...
雖已褪色，但…
We had a falling out.
我們不歡而散.
You went dark.
你誤入歧途了.
It's a dark business. Barney, Don't pretend you are not in it.
這就是撈偏門的. 巴尼，別想劃清界線.
The bad is survived, those are the rules I didn't make them up.
禍害遺千年，這是常規，非我捏造.
You see Barney here was contend to work for the samlling money as an employee.
你們看，巴尼當個員工，只為蠅頭小利就接工作.
And being a boss is more lucrative.
而當老闆可賺進大把鈔票.
But that's a concept that somehow eluded you.
為何你們都搞不懂.
Plus you got that pesky moral conscience.
加上你們的高道德良心.
God, that stuff gets away.
靠，這東西真煩人.
He thinks he is the good guy.
他總自認是好人.
Keep talking while you can.
有屁盡量放吧.
Sure, you got conscience that makes you weak
當然，你有道德，讓你心軟
Success, real Success...
成功，真正的成就…
is been willing to do the things that other people are not.
是願意做別人不想幹的事.
Not everyone is sick as you.
並非人人如你這般變態.
Oh, But you are.
哦，你就是.
Did you kill anyone today, Barney?   Blow any shit up?
你今天殺人了嗎，巴尼？ 炸了多少東西？
How about you kids?   Kill anyone?
你們呢，小鬼？ 殺人了嗎？
Before you all start grabbing bricks...
在你們開始抓起磚頭…
to stone me at The Hague.
想在海牙審判我之前.
I might wanna check your own hands for blood.
我想確認你們雙手是否已鮮血淋漓.
Oh, but I digress, where was I, yes.
噢，我離題了，我說到哪？ 對了.
Business is booming, right?
生意蒸蒸日上，對嗎？
A chopper here, a missile there.   Guns... whatever.
這一架直升機，那一枚導彈. 槍炮… 沁菜啦.
When suddenly a competitor.
忽然來個競爭對手.
If you can call "Uncle Sam" a competitor.
若你們可以稱競爭對手為〝山姆大叔〞.
Hires my own team.
徵召了我的團隊.
Barney and the whole gang to whack me.
巴尼和他組員圍剿我.
Things got ugly, real fast and a lot of people got dead
事情急轉直下，很快，死了很多人.
Three former brothers were in arms.
三位患難弟兄死在懷裏.
Shut your mouth.
別說了.
Three Expendables.
三個浴血團員.
Our brothers, men we ate with, fought with, blood with, were dead
一起吃飯、一起戰鬥，生死與共的兄弟死了.
He put 3 slugs into my chest, thank God for body armoured.
他朝我胸口連開三槍，幸虧有防彈背心.
Raving, I thought I was dead.
哀號著，我以為鐵掛了.
Then the boogie's out with the casualty.
然後他捨棄傷患揚長而去.
All dead.
全死了.
Because you couldn't stay out of my business.
就因你不爽我的生意.
Shut your mouth.
你閉嘴.
Barney.
巴尼.
Go on, Do it.
來呀，射吧.
Come on.
快啊.
It's what he wants.
他想找碴
It's hard to fathom, I can't believe you forgot.
小不忍亂大謀，我真不敢相信你竟忘了.
What?
什麼？
That it's hard to beat an enemy when you live inside your own head.
當你活在自己的象牙塔，很難擊敗敵人.
See, you tie me up...
瞧，你綁住我…
like an animal.
如畜牲般
Leave me to the slaughter. You humiliated me.
讓我被虐殺. 你羞辱我
Disgraced me.
讓我丟臉.
Now, when the time comes to kill you,
現在，當要殺你的時機一到…
and it will. I will not use a weapon, I will use my hands.
就快了. 我不會用武器，只用雙手.
Because I want you to feel the way I feel right now.
因為我想讓你體會我目前的感受.
Since we were brothers.
誰叫我們是兄弟.
What's that?
那是什麼？
It's a GPS tracker.
是GPS跟蹤器.
GPS tracker.
GPS跟蹤器.
How about that?
厲害吧？
Hold it.
別開槍.
We may need them.
或許有用.
I need a body, find him.
死要見屍，去找.
Found him.
找到他了.
Call the boss.
通知老大.
What happend?
搞屁呀？
We found a shitstorm.
衰事連連.
It's gonna get worse.
還會更糟.
This came for you 10 minuets ago.
這是十分鐘前發來的視訊.
Hey, Barney.
嗨，巴尼.
My search party's dead, so I'm taking that you're still with us.
我的搜索隊都死了，所以我猜你還活著.
You should kill me when you had the chance...
你有機會時，當立馬殺了我…
Cause that's your last window, and it's gone.
最後空檔，已錯失了.
Now, I got something to show you.
來，精采畫面分享.
Leader Harpo.
會見 哈波.
Ground show.
葛藍秀.
Gumo and...
嘎莫 和…
Chica. Yeah...
奇卡，耶…
Hey, give old screw that slim, Cook. Just realy...
把那苗條的揪起來，庫克. 準備…
Personally, I chalk it up to collateral damage.
就我而言，這都歸類附加傷害.
I don't give a fuck.   But...
我才不在乎. 但…
I know you.
我暸你.
48 hours they're gone for good.
48小時後，他們永久消失.
Do you want them?
想救他們嗎？
Come to get them.
放馬過來.
What do you gonna do?
你要怎麼辦？
Wow, looking a little strung out there, kids.
哇，像個串燒大會呀，小鬼.
This is what you get for being pawns in Barney's moral chess game.
這就是你們在巴尼的道德棋戲裏當馬前卒的下場.
That one looks a little slack.
那傢伙似乎綁太鬆了.
You know, I feel most bad for you.
知道嗎，我對你們感到惋惜.
I don't give a shit how you feel.
我才不在乎你的屁感受.
I do, I have a daughter.
我在乎，我亦有一女.
I have feelings, anyway.
總之，我也有感情.
You know when the CIA... presume that's who you're working for.
當中情局… 我假設你們為其工作.
The CIA, am I right?
中情局，對嗎？
I bet you don't even know who you're working for
我賭你們為誰幹活都不清楚.
But for Barney.
但巴尼…
Do you know who he is working for?
你們知道他為誰工作嗎？
Does he know who he is working...
他知道為誰工…
It's very confusing.
這非常困惑.
Anyway, when the CIA want the guys doing the dangerous work in the dangerous places.
總之，當中情局想找人在危險處做危險的工作.
They called us. When they didn't want to get their hands dirty...
他們派我們去. 當他們不想留下把柄時…
They called us.
他們又叫我們去.
Yep, we cleared every hotspot they had.
對，我們清除所有障礙.
We bomb the bad guys.
我們打擊壞人.
So the good guys could roll in looking like heroes.
然後好人搖身一變成了英雄.
We killed a lot.
我們殺人無數.
But we saved more lives...than you can possibly imagine.
但援救的人…比你們想的更多.
Then...
然而…
The boys on the hill wanting no loose ends.
高層傢伙想見好就收.
Try to bury me.
設法滅了我.
I was an american.
我是美國人.
Working for America.
為美國效命.
Was.
曾是.
They'd eat their own children.
他們竟狙殺自家人.
The lesson here is.
這學到的是…
Never do business with the government.
絕不跟政府做生意.
I'll gonna save you that heartache.
我會撫慰你們的心痛.
You never will.
你卻從來不會.
So you're getting your old team?
你要去找老隊員嗎？
Nah, I've burned that bridge.
不，我已斷絕關係.
You know, your pride is gonna get you killed.
知道嗎，你的自尊心會害死你.
Better me than them.
我死好過他們死.
So you really gonna go back?
你真的要回去救他們？
Yeah.
是的.
Alone?
單獨？
Yeah.
是的.
You're an idiot.
你是蠢蛋.
Thanks for showing up.
感謝告知.
I guess our favors are done.
我猜我們的好感消失了.
But you're still an idiot.
但你仍是白痴.
How the hell did you find me?
你如何找到我的？
People talk and I hear things.
別人談論，我探聽.
You got a mission.
你有任務.
I can help.
我能幫忙.
My name is... Galgo.
我叫…嘎戈.
Let me fill you in.
讓我上場吧.
I am good.
我很好.
Very good.
非常棒.
at warfare.
戰鬥中更強.
good memery, not afraid of anything.
記憶佳，無所懼.
I want to be your friend.
我想當你的朋友.
I don't need a friend.
我不需要朋友.
Yes, you do.
要，你需要.
Everybody does.
人人都需要.
I... don't have any friends, that's why I know
我…沒有朋友…所以我很明白.
Besides my friendship issues,
除了友誼問題.
What I really need now is something to do.
現在我真正要的是有事幹.
Well, not just anything.   But...
噢，並非啥事都幹. 但…
were I was born to do.
我是天生殺手.
Best bet, this is a one way trip.
最好打算，是有去無回.
Excuse me, sir.   But...
抱歉，老大. 但…
One way trip...
能亮相…
is better than no way trip.
總比沒戲唱好.
Which is the way I live now.
這就是我目前的寫照.
Help me with the grenade.
幫我抬這箱手榴彈.
I'm sorry.
對不起.
On the plane, Gogo.
放飛機上，戈戈.
On the plane, yes, sir.
放飛機上，遵命.
Gogo?   No Gogo.
戈戈？ 不叫戈戈.
Galgo, Galgo.
是嘎戈，嘎戈.
Galgo, Gogo sounds like a Parisian hooker.
嘎戈. 戈戈聽起來像巴黎妓女.
I am the bridegroom of death.
這是《新郎之死》.
The lyrics of a Spanish legion old songs that we used to sing when we were on a mission in Croatia.
西班牙的老軍歌，當我們在克羅埃西亞執行任務的時候經常唱.
That's where I met Mingo.
我就是在那遇上明戈.
The best point man ever.
最好的偵察兵.
Some kind of a savant, you don't know?
某種學者，你知道嗎？
ambush, this guy could sniff.
埋伏時，只聞呼吸聲.
But under fire, the coolest cut ever.
交戰時，殺無赦.
Just pure ice in his veins.
冷酷無情.
We were pinned down once.
有次我們被包圍.
two bullets left.
只剩兩顆子彈.
I looked over.
放眼望去.
No one bead of sweat.
沒人流汗.
was warm.
很溫暖.
Yeah.
是.
Can I help you up there?
要我幫你嗎？
You're a mechanic now?
你現在變技師了？
Of course I am a mechanic.
當然，我就是技師.
I am whatever you need me to be, sir.
我是使命必達，老大.
OK, so just be quiet.
好，請安靜.
Ah, yes, sir.
哦，遵命.
Tiger.
泰哥.
The sniper I knew, this guy got it all figured out.
狙擊手，這傢伙完全掌握.
Wind speed, temperature
風速、溫度.
shit barometric pressure.
大氣壓力.
But you know what he says the most important?
但你知道他說最重要的為何？
No.
不.
Patience.
耐心.
Really?
真的？
Yeah, he said that.
是，他說的
This thing smells good.
這東西好香啊.
What is that?   kerosene?   gasoline?   Or what is that?
是什麼？ 煤油？ 汽油？ 到底是什麼？
Aviation fuel.
航空燃料.
Good.   It's good.
讚，真好聞.
The best team member ever.
我見過最好的隊友
His name was Torres.
他名叫托雷斯.
Holy shit.
哇哩咧.
You wouldn't believe what this guy was capable to do.
你絕不信這傢伙的本事.
Un... be... lie... vable.   I'm telling you...
難…以…置…信. 我告訴你哦…
Galgo.
嘎戈.
Yeah, sir?
是，老大？
I think I know why your team let you go.
我終於了解你的團隊為何剔除你了.
You do?
你瞭？
Really?
真的？
Yes.
太棒了.
Last chance,
最後機會，
You sure you wanna do this?
你確定要接這工作？
I like traveling.
我喜歡旅行.
Good.
好吧.
Uh, who are those guys?
呃，那些傢伙是誰？
My old team.
我的老團隊.
What the hell are you doing here?
你們來幹什麼？
You're stupid enough to get yourself into this mess.
你蠢斃了才讓自己陷入困境.
We are the only ones trying up to get you out of it.
我們是唯一能救你脫困的人.
Come on, we're late for a war.
上來吧，我們打仗要遲到了.
Galgo, you might want to get off that seat, Christmas is coming.
嘎戈，你得讓出這個位子，耶誕節快來了.
But it's... June.
但…才六月吔.
Galgo, get the hell out.
嘎戈，到後面去.
Yes, sir.
遵命.
Thanks for the hat, bros.
謝謝你的帽子，兄弟.
Woah.
哇
I'm curious.
我很好奇.
What?
什麼？
Since when suicide become your hobby?
從何時起，自殺成為你的嗜好了？
I got a will.
我遺囑立好了.
You know, I'm probably the only friend you have.
知道嗎，我可能是你唯一的朋友.
I got lots of friends.
我有很多朋友.
You walk into your room, people jump on the tables.
當你走進房間，別人都得跳桌子上.
I missed you, Christmas.
我想死你了，耶誕節.
I missed you too, you demented bastard.
我也想你，瘋狂的混蛋.
You could love to do demented.
你就愛幹瘋狂的事.
It's kind of a solid structure.
那是個固體結構.
That is taking us one place to another, to unbelievable speeds.
用難以置信的速度，帶我們從甲地到乙地.
Think about it.
想想吧.
If...If God.
若…老天.
If God, if he would like us.
若老天喜歡我們.
You would fly.
你就能飛.
He would give us feathers.
他會給我們羽毛.
Do you have feathers?
你有羽毛嗎？
Do you have feathers?   I don't have feathers.
你有羽毛嗎？ 我沒有羽毛.
Damn! It's gonna be a long ass flight, fellows.
靠！ 夥伴們，這將是個長途飛行.
It's going to be.
確實是.
It's going to be a long flight, but.
確實是個漫長的飛行，但…
Do not worry, I'm here, man.
別擔心，兄弟，我在這兒.
Because I can't sleep on planes.
因為我在飛機上睡不著.
Yeah?
請講？
I thought you should know, Barney.
巴尼，我想你應該知道.
You're walking a new shitstorm.
你們正踏上危險之旅.
NSA ran the signals and frequencies check on your team's phones.
國安局搜尋了你隊員的手機信號和頻率.
This bastard is not even trying to hide them.
這混蛋根本沒打算把他們藏起來.
Where is he taking them?
他把人帶哪去了？
They're in Afghanistan.
他們在阿富汗.
Another honeymoon hotspot.
另一個蜜月熱點.
Who is that?
誰在說話？
Lee Christmas.
李·耶誕節.
Not far off, Christmas
快到了，耶誕節
Stonebanks' compound is where he trains his guns.
史通班克斯的場子，正是他訓練槍手的地方.
It's very heavily fortified.
戒備森嚴.
You show off the local army.
展示當地的軍隊.
I don't understand what this guy's saying.
我聽不懂這傢伙在說什麼.
Local army's status.
當地軍隊的情況.
Small, corrupt.
小型、腐敗.
Stonebanks got all the brass in his pocket.
史通班克斯把所有軍官收買了.
He's been running his operations through the shit hole of country for years.
多年來他一直透過那鬼地方操縱他的業務.
Wants some advice?
想要建議嗎？
What's the advice?
什麼建議？
What god damn language is that?
說哪國鳥話啦？
I'm gonna tell you I don't understand you either.
經價聽無力工瞎.
Look who's talking?
半斤八兩？
What's the advice, Drummer?
莊墨，有何建議？
Forget about what you're thinking.
先別想著救你的隊友.
Remember our deal.
記得我們的交易.
We need him alive.
我們要他活著.
So you can sit on the court room and beat him with technicality?
那麼你就可以坐在法院裏，用法律手段打敗他嗎？
Those are orders, Barney.
這是命令，巴尼.
You broke the phone.
你把手機砸了.
I got another one.
我還有別支.
You think we'll make it back on this one?
你認為我們這次能全身而退嗎？
You didn't have to come along, Christmas.
你無須跟來，耶誕節.
Sure, I did.
我必須來.
Morons need friends.
白癡需要朋友.
Gentlmen, change plans.
各位，改變計畫.
This is it?
就這樣？
This is your evacuate team?
這是你的撤離小組嗎？
Short notice.
通知時間太短.
Yeah, very short.
對，真短（矮）.
Where is your team, Major Drummer?
你的隊伍咧，莊墨少校？
No team, this one is off the books.
沒有，這行動非官方.
I'm not even here.
我從未出現.
Nobody is here.
沒人來過.
I thought Church was an asshole.
我曾以為〝恰吉〞是個混蛋.
Yeah, Hysterical is strength.
嗯，歇斯底里是强度.
We...   Weird concept.
奇… 奇怪的觀念.
I mean, if you're hysterically strong,
我是指，若你歇斯底里很強
You don't even have to go to the gym.
你甚至無需去健身館了.
You are just strong, you just got it, you just got it.
有志者事竟成.
Hysterical was a concept that actually was applied to women in the 19th century.
事實上這觀念在19世紀同樣適用於女人。
Authentic concept. You know what I mean?
觀念. 你懂我意思吧？
Well, this is a interesting place.
噢，這地方真不錯.
He gave me a migrine.
他讓我頭很痛.
I hear that.
我聽到了.
Look to the right side, if you ran out bullets.
往好處想，若子彈用盡.
You can talk them dead.
你能〝說〞死敵人.
Roger that.
明白.
Tall one doesn't like me.
大隻佬不喜歡我.
He didn't like anybody.
他不喜歡任何人.
Yeah.
是的.
What did you say?
你說什麼？
He likes you.
他喜歡你.
What the hell was that?
那是蝦咪碗糕？
What?
什麼？
The computer strapped your wrist.
電腦綁在手腕上.
Nothing.
沒你事.
The same thing you were busting the kids' balls about?
為這東西，你打了小孩的蛋蛋？
I had it for a while.
我用很久了.
Why did your team let you go?
前團隊為何要你走？
Why is the matter now?
這有關係嗎？
I wanna know who I am working with.
我想瞭解戰友.
They are not around anymore.
他們不在了.
So..
所以..
Listen.
聽著.
So why did they let you go?
他們為為何要你走？
They didn't.
他們沒有.
Mean got see.
老實說.
I was not in the army anymore, we were...
我不在軍隊了，我們…
retreaving a hostage something like uh...
帶著人質撤退.
like we are doing here.
就如現在一般.
It was a beatiful day.
那是個艷陽天.
No problems.
沒啥問題.
And then it all went bad.
然後，風雲突變.
We were hit, cut off.
我們受襲，失散了.
waiting for support.
等待救援.
No one came.
沒人來幫忙.
And...
然後…
Everybody died.
全體陣亡.
Except me.
就剩我.
Mingo,
明戈…
Torres and Tiger, right?
托雷斯和老虎，對嗎？
You were listening.
你有在聽.
Yeah, I'm listening.
是，我在聽.
Thank you!
感謝！
So what do you think?
你有何想法？
I think we should get this over with.
我覺得該速戰速決.
Four signals.
四個標兵.
8 stories up.
上有八個.
This is the way too wrong.
真是個不歸路.
Cause I don't like it.
不是說我討厭它.
You know he's got eyes on us now.
你明知他現在盯著我們.
May I suggest something?
我能插個話嗎？
- No.     - No, later.
-不行  -不，晚點再說.
That's what I thought.
我想也是.
It's fine.
沒關係.
Go.
走了.
Break it.
破門.
What the hell?
奈啊內？
Hey, Barney.
嘿，巴尼.
I knew you couldn't stay away.
我知道你不會撒手不管的.
But I'm relieved someone to pick up the kids.
終於放心有人來帶走小鬼.
You've gotta been there.
你們已經到了吧.
Now try to get them out.
現在設法救他們出去吧.
But unfortunatelly for you.
但不幸的是.
The entire complex has been wired with C4.
整個建築群都裝上了C4炸藥.
Let's take a regular joke, was 90 seconds to get out there, you got...
我們用規律的把戲，90秒逃出去，你就…
How about 45?
45秒如何？
He's turned the whole place into a bomb.
他把整個地方變成一個炸彈.
Maybe not.
還有救.
9% battery, pal, you didn't incharge it?
9%電池，兄弟，你沒充電嗎？
Excuse me, but what are you doing?
打擾一下，但…你在幹嘛？
Try some code, should be jammed the signal.
重設編碼，應該能干擾信號.
Why didn't you think of that?
你為何想不到呢？
I used it to check the weather.
我只用來看天氣.
Will you just shut up, let him do this thing?
你們惦惦，讓他做事好嗎？
You're sure you can do this, Thorn?
你確定行嗎，索恩？
I can do it. I can do it.
我能搞定，我行的.
- Come on, man.     - Come on, dude.
-加油，兄弟.  -快呀，哥哥
Come on, Come on.
加油，加油.
Come on, Thorn.
加油，索恩.
Give me a second.
給我幾秒.
Come on.
快點.
Focus.
專注.
Got it!
搞定！
Not bad. Good work.
不錯，厲害.
We've lost the overwrite.   And the signal is jamed.
我們失去操控，信號被阻擋了.
Send them in.
部隊進攻.
Barney, the battery is 8%. When this thing dies, we lose override.
巴尼，電量還有8%. 當電池告罄，我們就失去控制了.
It gives us 25 minutes tops.
頂多撐25分鐘.
Don't pop the bottles yet.
先別管電池了.
We still got trouble.
還有麻煩.
- What?     - Big trouble.
-吓？  -大難臨頭.
Lucky again bro.
狗屎運哪.
Try to enjoy the view.   Because...
快享受風景吧. 因為…
shortly the building that you're currently standing in...
你們所在的建築物…
will be surrounded by the Afghanistan amy.
將被阿富汗軍隊包圍了.
Shit.
靠.
How did you shitheads manage to get captured anyway?
你們這幫呆瓜怎麼被抓的？
Shut your mouth.
你閉嘴.
Stay back.
退後.
It's not an accident.
這非意外事件.
And we're been trapped here.
而我們被困在此處.
It is exactly what you knew will happen.
你們心知肚明會發生何事.
Us, terrorised each other.
我們…相互指責.
It stops now.
該停止了.
We can do this.
我們能搞定的.
But only if we do this...
但成功唯一要件…
together.
團結.
If we work as a team.
若我們合作無間.
We just made to get out this alive.
我們才能虎口逃生.
Now do you... wanna make it work.
你們…想逃出升天.
That's simple.
輕而易舉.
You got weapons?
你有武器嗎？
Here's the plan.
計畫如下.
We're gonna break out to small groups and go out to the ground floor.
我們分成幾個小隊，並前往大廳.
Get ready.
就緒.
Come on.
行動.
Thorn, you stay with me.
索恩，跟著我.
You take Galgo.
你帶嘎戈.
I don't want to.
我才不要.
- What, what?   You let me...     - Shhhh!
-幹嘛？ 你…  -噓！
Quiet.
安靜.
Don't stop, one there, one there.
別停，一左，一右.
There's too many.
敵人太多了.
You're on the flank, bring them to halt. bring it.
你到側面，阻止他們.
That's enough, light them up.
玩夠了，轟了他們.
Incoming!
炮彈來襲！
Up the shaft, Thorn. You gotta protect that signal jammer.
索恩，爬上去. 你得保護信號干擾器.
I thought you can fight.
我以為你多能打呢.
Jesus God, are you OK?
哇哩咧，你還好吧？
Terrified, I love this.
超可佈，我愛死了.
Good, keep moving.
讚，繼續走.
Relax.
放輕鬆.
I told you, you would give yourself a stroke.
我說過，你會搞到中風的.
Drummer?
莊墨？
You got a tank problem, pal.
你有坦克大麻煩，老兄.
Do something about it.
快幫我解決.
I'm on it.
上場了.
Trench, on your right.
陳菊，你右邊.
That's gotta hurt.
肯定很痛.
Drummer's in the house.
莊墨作主了.
Hey, look!
嘿，瞧！
Let's go.
閃人.
I am pick up that tempo, boys.
我跟上拍子了，兄弟.
Look out for the chopper.
小心直升機.
Not good.
不妙.
Hold on.
抓緊.
This is not happened.
真不可思議.
You wanna do something.
該你行動了
Oh, shit.
完了.
Hi, there!
嗨，妳好！
Closer.
靠近點.
再近一點.
Yang, get something.
楊，幹掉它.
Next.
下一台.
Your name is Luna, right?   Luna means moon.
妳名叫露娜，對嗎？  露娜是月亮之意.
Hypnotic, mysterious, magical, like yourself.
催眠、神秘、魔幻，人如其名.
Would you like to hold...
你願意握住…
my gun?
我的槍嗎？
Goodbye, sweet.
掰掰，甜心
- There he is!     - Fire!
-他在那！  -發射！
Come on, drive this thing.
快點，啟動坦克.
This one's for Caesar, assholes.
這為凱薩賞你的，混蛋.
Yeah!
耶！
Damn, that's cool.
靠，真酷.
It's all under control.
一切易如反掌.
That's what it looks like.
您說了算.
Come on.
加油.
This the happiest moment of my life.
這是我此生最爽時刻
Jingling jingling.
叮叮噹噹
Do you finish here?
搞完沒？
Man.
男人.
- You're not gonna believe this.     - Oh, God.
-你不會相信的.  -天哪.
I've been thinking about you the whole time.
我無時無刻想著妳.
- During the whole fight!     - Can we just go?
-就在戰鬥之時！  -能走先嗎？.
Come on.
來吧.
Hold on.
抓緊.
Where did you learn how to fly?
你在哪學飛行的？
Vietnam.
越南.
Barney, we got reinforcements.
巴尼，他們派兵增援
Shit.
哇咧.
Drummer.
莊墨.
There's another wave coming.
敵軍再臨.
The only way is up.
活路只剩屋頂.
On my way.
立馬到.
Evacuate in 5.
五分鐘後撤退.
Got it.
收到.
Everybody get to the roof, now.
所有人上屋頂，快！
Got it.
收到.
Trench, Yang, come on, clear the roof.
陳菊、楊，屋頂淨空.
Let's go.
走吧.
Damn.
靠.
- Always this easy?     - Pretty much.
-總是輕而易舉？  -易如反掌.
How hard can it be to kill 10 men?
殺10個人能有多難？
D'you think you could even just wound a couple?
難道你們就無法撂倒2、3個嗎？
Watch closely.
看仔細了.
And again.
再一個.
Anybody else?
誰還要試？
Useness.
一群廢物.
You want something done, right?
你們要我出手，是吧？
You got valet parking here?
這裡有代客泊車嗎？
Yeah, there's some right here.
有，就在此處.
Go, go, go.
快點走.
Don't stop.
別停.
Come on, guys, move it.
加油，兄弟，快跑.
Drummer, we were pinned down.
莊墨，我們被困住了.
Stop bumbling.
別靠腰了.
Good morning.
早安.
Let's get to the chopper.
快上直升機！
Let's go.
出發.
Go, go, go.
快點走.
Move, go, go.
動作快.
Go, gotta go.
快，得走了.
Yang.
楊.
You're welcome.
無需言謝.
You're working for Trench.
你替〝陳菊〞工作.
Yeah.
是.
He paid me more money.
他給我更多錢.
Who the hell are you?
您哪位呀？
I'm the guy just saved your ass.
剛剛救了你的人.
Battery is 2%.
電池剩2%.
Hey, Barney, leaving so soon?
嘿，巴尼，趕投胎嗎？
Come on, let's finish this.
來吧，做個了斷.
How you feeling?
感覺如何？
Come on, stand up, you'll feel better.
快，起來，你會舒服點.
Barney, where are you?
巴尼，你在哪？
Lose the armour, I want you to feel this.
脫了防彈衣，我要你嘗嘗子彈的味道.
Barney, we gotta go.
巴尼，我們得走了.
Not even think about a gun for that things of garbage in the back.
別想偷偷拿藏在背後的暗槍.
Come on.
丟掉.
That's it. That's it.
這就對了.
We don't need this, do we?
我們不需要槍，對吧.
Come on.
起來.
Barney we gotta go!
巴尼，沒時間了！
Battery is 1%.
電池剩1%.
Come on, Barney.
快點，巴尼.
What about the Hague?
把我送海牙國際法庭如何？
I am the Hague.
我就是海牙.
Battery's gone.
電池沒電了.
Gotta go, gotta go.
要走了.
No, No, wait, wait.
不，再等等.
I can't wait.
不能等了.
Go.
衝.
Come on, Barney, go!
加油，巴尼. 快！
What the hell.
管它的
You will make it, Barney.
巴尼，你能做到的.
- Barney!     - Barney!
-巴尼！  -巴尼！
Holy shit!
哇哩咧！
Pull me up.
拉我上去.
You'll gonna fire us again, Barney.
你又會解雇了我們，巴尼.
Come on.
拜託.
Can't hear you, pal!
聽不見，老兄
I'm gonna kill you.
我要殺了你.
All right. I'm sorry.
好啦，對不起.
Pull me up, you idiots.
拉我上去，白痴們.
Don't pull him up. Haha~
別拉他上來. 哈哈～
To Caesar!
敬凱撒！
Yeah.
耶！
Yo, Barney.
喲，巴尼.
Yeah.
是.
I don't think I don't need this anymore.
我認為我再也不需要這個了.
You want your luck back?
你不想幸運再臨嗎？
I hope I didn't stretch it.
希望我沒撐大它.
I think you did stretch it.
你真的搞大了.
- Good to have you back man.     - Good to be back.
-你回來真好，兄弟.  -很高興歸隊
Don't scare us like that anymore, ok.
不准再嚇我們了，好嗎.
Hail Caesar.
哈囉，凱撒.
To me.
乾杯.
You never got him to the Hague.
你沒把他抓到海牙國際法庭.
You know, Drummer.
知道嗎，莊墨.
Working with you ain't been so bad.
與你共事沒那麼糟.
I haven't had so much fun in years.
好多年沒這麼爽了.
Fun's important.
爽才是王道.
These guys are nuts.
這些傢伙是瘋子.
Our arms combine here.
我們團結一心.
I'm fire.
我是火.
Yeah, you are.
好，你是.
Oh, come on, if you have to be....
噢，拜託，如果你…
Are you calling Captain Planet?
你們在呼叫行星隊長嗎？
You'll have to be a planet here.
你會成為一個明星的.
Oh, Major old school.
噢，老派少校.
Hey, Major bad ass.
嘿，惡棍少校.
I am sure.
我確定.
I have done enough that I am worth my weight... in gold, you know.
我做的事，足夠價值與我體重相等的黃金.
Am I close?
很接近了吧？
I am...since I am as crazy as you.
我…自從我跟你一樣瘋狂.
I am sure of fitting..One...
我相信我很適合這個工作.
Galgo.
嘎戈.
Yeah, sir.
是，老大.
Welcome aboard.
歡迎入團.
Thank god, because I already spent a fortune on this.
謝主隆恩，因為我已花了家當做紋身.
You know what I mean. I am so happy.
你懂我意思嗎？ 我咍翻了！
Barne, thank you!
巴尼，感謝您！
No, no, no, no hugging, no.
不～別逾矩，不准.
No hugging, no hugging, No...
不擁，不抱，不…
Best two at the three.
三戰兩勝.
Hey.
嗨.
Just want to say "Thanks".
只想說聲〝謝謝〞.
For what?
為何？
For caring.
承蒙照顧.
Oh, come on.
哦，不足掛齒.
Yeah, Thanks!
嗯，謝啦！
You know, If you were 30 years younger...
知道嗎，若你年輕30歲…
I will be afraid of you.
我會躲著妳的.
Cherrs.
乾杯.
Hey, Yang.
嗨，楊.
Looks like you got to grow spurt.
似乎瞬間長高了點啊.
Tall people don't live long.
個高不長命.
So you're working for Trench now.
所以你現在為陳菊工作了.
And you, I thought you retired.
而你，我以為你退休了.
I lied.
我撒了謊.
Good.
讚.
You guys wanna get a room?
您倆要不要開房間啊？
We gonna need a room.
我們是需要開間房.
So jealous.
吃醋吧.
We came this thing together.
我們因此事相聚.
You gonna leave it go.
你就得忘掉不開心的事兒.
Absolutely.
正是如此.
You hear it?
聽懂了吧？
- Cheers.     - Cheers.
-乾杯.  -乾杯.
You know for a guy that doesn't take orders very well.
知道嗎，在那些不聽命令的人之中.
You did pretty good.
你幹的很好.
Yeah?
真的？
So when do I take over?
那何時生意歸我管？
Keep drinking.
想得美.
Hey, Smilee.
嘿，斯麥利.
Get over here.
過來.
You did good, kid.
你幹得好，小子.
♪ Old man look at my life, ♪
♫ Neil Young 《 Old Man 》
♪ I'm a lot like you were. ♪
♪ Old man look at my life, ♪
♪ Twenty four and there's so much more. ♪
♪ Live alone in a paradise, ♪
♪ That makes me think of two. ♪
♪ Love lost, such a cost, ♪
♪ Give me things that don't get lost. ♪
You look like a proud demented father.
你看似個驕傲的瘋老爹.
Could you skip the "demented" apart?
你能把〝瘋狂〞拿掉嗎？
It was a compliment.
這是致敬呢.
hey5377880pchome.com.tw
感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感
感感　感感感感感感感感感　感感感感
感感感　感　　　　　　　　　感感感
感　感感感感感感　感感感　感感感感
感感　感感　感感　感感感　　感感感
感感感感　感　感　感感感　感　感感
感　　　感感感　感感感感　感　感感
感感　感感感感　感　　　　感感感感
感感　感感感　感感感感　感感感感感
感感感感感感感感　感感感感感　感感
感　　　　　　　　　　　　　　　感
感感感感感感感　　感感感感感感感感
感感感感感　　感　　　感感感感感感
感感感　　感感感　感感　　感感感感
感　　感感感感感　感感感感　　　感
感感感感感感感感　感感感感感感感感
感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感感
謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝
謝謝謝　　謝謝謝謝謝　　謝　謝謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝　謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝　　　　　　　　　　謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝謝
謝　　　　　謝　　　　　　　　謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝　謝謝　謝謝謝　謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝　　　　　　　　謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝　　　　　　　　　　謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝　謝謝謝　謝謝謝
謝謝謝　謝謝謝謝謝謝謝　　　謝謝謝
謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝謝
收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收
收收收收　　收收收收收　　收收收收
收收　收　收收收收收收　收收收收收
收收　收　收收收　　　　　　　收收
收收　　　　　收收收收　收收收收收
收　收收　收收收收收收　收收收收收
收　收收　收收　　　　　　　　　收
收收收收　收　收收收收收　收收收收
收收收收　　收收收收收收　收　收收
收收收　　收收　　　　　　　　　收
收　　　　收收收收收收收　收收收收
收收　收　收收　收收收收　收收收收
收收收收　收收收　　收收　收收收收
收收收收　收收收收收收收　收收收收
收收收收　收收收收收　　　收收收收
收收收收　收收收收收收　收收收收收
收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收收
看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看
看看看看　　看看看看　　看看看看看
看看看看　看看　看看　看看看看看看
看　　　　　　　　看　看看看　看看
看看看看看看看看看看　　　　　　看
看看　　看看　看看看　看看看　看看
看看　看看看看　看看　看看看　看看
看看　看看　看　看　看　看看　看看
看　看　看　看看看　看　看　看看看
看看看　看　看看　看看　看　看看看
看看看看　看看看看看看看　看看看看
看看看　看　看看看看看看　看看看看
看看看　看看　看看看看　看　看看看
看看　看看看　看看看看　看看　看看
看　看看看看看看看看　看看看　看看
看看看看看看看看　　看看看看看　看
看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看看